dialyou.com 2015-12-09

# DialYou - Privacy Policy - dialyou.com

In the way of register for and availing various services we provides from time to time throughout our website which is www.dialyou.com ("Website", telephone & search) or any other standard in which Dial You may provides services (collectively referred to as "Media") you may be obligate to give your name, residence address, place of work address, email address, date of birth, educational experience and related Personal Information ("Personal Information").

Basically, The Personal Information is used for three specific purposes to modify the content you see, to accomplish your requests for assured services, and to contact you regarding our services by the use of include but not limited to email's, sms's and other resources of message. Except otherwise stated unambiguously, this Policy is applying to Personal Information as disclose in any field of the media.

We are devoted to defending the privacy and privacy of all Personal Information that you may share as a user of Media In furtherance thereof, we have this policy to revealed our good assurance.

This policy does not apply to the practice of organizations that we do not own or to people that we do not retain or supervise.

Personal Information will be set aside classified and will be used for our research, marketing, and tactical client scrutiny objectives and other internal business purposes only. We do not sell or rent Personal Information apart from that in case you are a customer of our search services through any of the Media, your Personal Information shall be shared with our subscribers/advertisers and you shall be deem to have given approval to the same. Further, the subscribers / advertisers who are programmed with us, may call you, based on the question or enquiry that you make with us, enquiring about any

Product / Service or Product / Service of any subscriber / advertiser or Product / Service of any exacting subscriber / advertiser.

We will share Personal Information only under one or more of the subsequent situation: - If we have your consent or deemed consent to do so - If we are obligated by law (including court orders) to do so. In furtherance of the discretion with which we treat Personal Information we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and administrative dealings to safeguard and secured the information we collect online.

We give you the capability to edit your account information and preference at any time, including whether you want us to contact you about new services. To protecting your privacy and security, we will also take sensible steps to verify your identity before conceding right of entry or making corrections.

You recognize that you are disclose Personal Information willingly. preceding to the completion of any registration process on our website or prior to availing of any services obtainable on our website if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may renounce from doing so; however if you don't provide information that is requested, it is possible that the registration procedure would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail of the our services.

If you are our commercial customer, it is possible that we have entered into a convention with you for non-disclosure of private information. This Policy shall not influence such a contract in any mode.

If you have query or concern about these privacy policies; please send us an email at 

md@dialyou.com

**Jurisdiction:** any Dispute arising out of or in conjunction with this agreement shall be referred to the Fatehabad court only.
